export const data = [
    {
        question:"Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
        option1: "Modem",
        option2: "Router",
        option3: "LAN cable",
        option4: "Pen Drive",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question: "When rendering a list using the JavaScript map() method, what is required for each element rendered?",
        option1: "data",
        option2: "key",
        option3: "id",
        option4: "index",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the children prop?",
        option1: "A property that adds child values to state",
        option2: "A property that lest you set an object as a property",
        option3: "A property lest you nest components in other components",
        option4: "A property that lest you pass data to child components",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
        option1: "npx create-react-app myReactApp",
        option2: "npm create-react-app myReactApp",
        option3: "npx create-react-app",
        option4: "npm create-react-app",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"What is the correct syntax to import a Component from React?",
        option1: "import React.Components from 'react' ",
        option2: "import [ Component ] from 'react'",
        option3: "import { Component } from 'react'",
        option4: "import Component from 'react'",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question:"Find the bug in this code: function car({make, model}) {return <h1>{make} {model}</h1>;};",
        option1: "Remove the return statement ",
        option2: "Add parenthesis around the return value'",
        option3: "The first letter of the functions must be capitalized'",
        option4: "Wrap the return in a fragment'",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question:"React separates the user interface into components. How are components combinded to create a user interface?",
        option1: "With webpack ",
        option2: "By nesting components",
        option3: "By putting them in a folder structure",
        option4: "with code splitting'",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question:"What command is used to start the React local development server?",
        option1: "npm run dev ",
        option2: "npm serve",
        option3: "npm build",
        option4: "npm start",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?",
        option1: "constant",
        option2: "var",
        option3: "let",
        option4: "const",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question: "A copy of the 'real' DOM that is kept in memory is called what?",
        option1: "Virtual DOM",
        option2: "DOM",
        option3: "Shadow DOM",
        option4: "React DOM",
        ans:1,
    },


];
